<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<!-- * PopulateDatabase.xml * * Copyright (C) 2017 Universidad de Sevilla 

	* * The use of this project is hereby constrained to the conditions of the 

	* TDG Licence, a copy of which you may download from * http://www.tdg-seville.info/License.html -->

<beans xmlns="http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans http://www.springframework.org/schema/beans/spring-beans.xsd">

	<!-- User accounts -->
	<bean id="userAccountAdministrator" class="security.UserAccount">
		<property name="username" value="admin" />
		<property name="password" value="21232f297a57a5a743894a0e4a801fc3" />
		<property name="authorities">
			<list>
				<bean class="security.Authority">
					<property name="authority" value="ADMIN" />
				</bean>
			</list>
		</property>
	</bean>
	
	<!-- Administrator -->
	<bean id="administrator" class="domain.Administrator">
		<property name="name" value="Administrator" />
		<property name="surname" value="1" />
		<property name="emailAddress" value="administrator@acme.com" />
		<property name="userAccount" ref="userAccountAdministrator" />
	</bean>
	
	<!-- Internationalization -->
	
	<bean id="internationalization1" class="domain.Internationalization">

		<property name="countryCode" value="es" />
		
		<property name="messageCode" value="term.condition" />

		<property name="value" value="INFORMACIÓN RELEVANTE

Es requisito necesario para el uso de la web que lea y acepte los siguientes Términos y
	Condiciones que a continuación se redactan. El uso de nuestros
	servicios implicará que usted
	ha leído y aceptado los Términos y Condiciones de Uso en el presente
	documento. 
	
	INFORMACIÓN PERSONAL
	
	Un administrador puede puede borrar un periódico, artículo, chirp o anuncio si considera que afecta moralmente a otros usuarios.
	Si cualquier usuario quiere borrar algún dato personal y la aplicación no le ofrece la posibilidad de hacerlo, debe ponerse en contacto con aisscreamacas@gmail.com


	COMPROBACIÓN ANTIFRAUDE

La compra del usuario puede ser aplazada para la comprobación
	antifraude. También puede ser suspendida por más tiempo para una
	investigación más rigurosa, para evitar transacciones fraudulentas.

	PRIVACIDAD

Este sitio web www.acme.com garantiza que la información personal que usted envía
	cuenta con la seguridad necesaria. Los datos ingresados por usuario  no serán
	entregados a terceros, salvo que deba ser revelada en cumplimiento a
	una orden judicial o requerimientos legales.

Acme-Newspaper reserva los derechos de cambiar o de modificar
	estos términos sin previo aviso.
	
	LEGISLACIÓN APLICABLE
El Aviso Legal y las Condiciones Generales de Uso se rigen por las siguientes normas:

La Ley 34/2002, de 11 de julio, de Services de la Sociedad de la Información y de Comercio Electrónico (LSSI-CE) (particularmente, su artículo 10).
La Ley Orgánica 15/1999, de 13 de diciembre, de Protección de Datos de Carácter Personal (LOPD).
El Real Decreto 1720/2007, de 21 de diciembre, por el que se aprueba el Reglamento de desarrollo de la Ley Orgánica 15/1999, de 13 de diciembre, de Protección de Datos de Carácter Personal." />

	</bean>
	
	<bean id="internationalization2" class="domain.Internationalization">

		<property name="countryCode" value="en" />
		
		<property name="messageCode" value="term.condition" />

		<property name="value" value="RELEVANT INFORMATION 

 It is a necessary requirement for the use of this web, that you read and accept the following Terms and
Conditions that are written below. The use of our
services will mean that you have read and accepted the Terms and Conditions of Use in this
document. 

 PERSONAL INFORMATION
 
 
An administrator can delete a newspaper, article, chirp or advertisement if think that it affects other users morally.
If any user wants to delete some personal data and the application does not have the possibility to do that, you should contact with aisscreamacas@gmail.com


 ANTI-FRAUD VERIFICATION 

 The user's purchase can be postponed for checking
anti fraud. It can also be suspended for a longer time for a
more rigorous investigation, to avoid fraudulent transactions. 

 PRIVACY 

This site web www.acme.com guarantees that the personal information you send
has the necessary security. The data entered by user will not be
delivered to third parties, unless it must be disclosed in compliance with
an order

Acme-Newspaper reserves the rights to change or modify
these terms without prior notice.

   APPLICABLE LEGISLATION 
    
 The  Legal Notice and the General Conditions of Use  are governed by the following rules: 

The Law 34/2002, of 11 July, on Services of the Society of Information and Electronic Commerce (LSSI-CE)(particularly, article 10).
The Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13, Protection of Personal Data (LOPD).
The Royal Decree 1720/2007, of December 21, which approves the Regulation of development of the Organic Law 15/1999, of December 13, Protection of Personal Data." />

	</bean>
	
	<!-- Configuration -->
	<bean id="configuration1" class="domain.Configuration">
		<property name="tabooWords">
			<list>
				<value>viagra</value>
				<value>cialis</value>
				<value>sex</value>
				<value>sexo</value>
			</list>
		</property>
	</bean>
	
	
	<!-- Folder -->
	<bean id="folder1ad1" class="domain.Folder">

		<property name="name" value="in box" />

		<property name="system" value="true" />
		
		<property name="childrenFolders">

			<list>

			</list>

		</property>

		<property name="actor" ref="administrator" />

	</bean>

	<bean id="folder2ad1" class="domain.Folder">

		<property name="name" value="out box" />

		<property name="system" value="true" />

		<property name="childrenFolders">

			<list>

			</list>

		</property>

		<property name="actor" ref="administrator" />

	</bean>

	<bean id="folder3ad1" class="domain.Folder">

		<property name="name" value="notification box" />

		<property name="system" value="true" />

		<property name="childrenFolders">

			<list>

			</list>

		</property>

		<property name="actor" ref="administrator" />

	</bean>

	<bean id="folder4ad1" class="domain.Folder">

		<property name="name" value="trash box" />

		<property name="system" value="true" />

		<property name="childrenFolders">

			<list>

			</list>

		</property>

		<property name="actor" ref="administrator" />

	</bean>

	<bean id="folder5ad1" class="domain.Folder">

		<property name="name" value="spam box" />

		<property name="system" value="true" />

		<property name="childrenFolders">

			<list>

			</list>

		</property>

		<property name="actor" ref="administrator" />

	</bean>
	
	
	
</beans>